buzzzy.com 2014-03-31

# 

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

### Last Updated: December 2013

[**TheSocialCV.com**](https://thesocialcv.com/) (“TSCV”) and Dice Holdings, Inc are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while providing personalized career management services.

Note: Any reference to 'we' or 'us', 'our' or website are references to the website **www.TheSocialCV.com** (the “Website”) and our service platform (TheSocialCV.com). TheSocialCV.com provides links to the websites of many other companies to which this policy does not apply. We cannot, and do not, assume responsibility for the privacy or information policies, practices or actions of any third parties.

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how we treat personally identifiable information we collect from visitors to the Website, how we use the personally identifiable information that we have collected, and the ways you can access and correct your personally identifiable information.

TSCV respects the privacy settings of all the networks it measures. If you have a private account on a social network and you have not explicitly given TSCV access to your data it will not be analyzed. If you are creating public data but do not want it indexed by TSCV you can opt-out by simply emailing [support@thesocialcv.com](mailto:support@thesocialcv.com) Dice Holdings, Inc (the parent company of TSCV) has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements and the TRUSTed Cloud Program Requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personally identifiable information. The TRUSTe program covers information that is collected through the website, www.thesocialcv.com and our service platform (TheSocialCV.com). TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@thesocialcv.com](mailto:support@thesocialcv.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

Dice Holdings, Inc complies with the U.S. E.U. Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Dice Holdings, Inc has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Dice Holdings, Inc’s certification, please visit [http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/](https://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

## Information Collection and Use

**Information Collected Upon Registration.** If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to TSCV. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide us with, or that you decide to include in your public profile.

**Additional Information.** Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and find opportunities in the TSCV system. If you contact us by email through the Site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.

**Use of Contact Information.** In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

**Log Data.** When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data" ). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service.

### Cookies

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. TSCV may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

**Third Party Cookies.** The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, and to provide data to enhance the user experience.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons).** We might employ or a third party advertising partner might employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that would help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We would not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

**Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting.** We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here.](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will share your personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.

**Service Providers.** We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

We may also disclosure your personally identifiable information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process,
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * any other third party with your prior consent to do so,
  * TSCV may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

### Security

TSCV is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact [support@thesocialcv.com](mailto:support@thesocialcv.com).

### Social Media (Features) and Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Twitter and LinkedIn buttons and Facebook like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Blogs

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@thesocialcv.com](mailto:support@thesocialcv.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Links to Other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### Our Policy Towards Children

The Site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [support@thesocialcv.com](mailto:support@thesocialcv.com). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.

### Use of Data

TSCV indexes public data presents some of this data on [TheSocialCV.com](https://thesocialcv.com/). TSCV will never analyze your private data unless we are given explicit access.

If are not a TSCV user and wish to opt out of TSCV, simply email [support@thesocialcv.com](mailto:support@thesocialcv.com)

### Changing or Deleting Your Information

TSCV account holders may review, update, delete or correct the Personally Identifiable Information by logging into their account and accessing the “My Profile” section. You may also contact us at [support@thesocialcv.com](mailto:support@thesocialcv.com). If wish you to request your account to be deactivated, you may also email us at the address above. All access requests will be responded to within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Information Related to Data Collected from Clients

TSCV collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes.

TSCV has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the TSCV’s Client (the data controller). If the Client requests TSCV to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 days.

TSCV will retain personal data we process on behalf of our clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. TSCV will retain and use this personally identifiable information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Notification of Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Questions?

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to [support@thesocialcv.com](mailto:support@thesocialcv.com). You may also contact us at:

c/o WorkDigital Ltd  
Telephone House, 69-77 Paul Street  
London, EC2A 4NW  
Attention: Privacy Director
